[
    {
        "question" : "What is the derivative of x² + 1 with respect to x?",
        "answers": ["2x", "x", "x+1", "2x+1"],
        "correctAns": "2x"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the derivative of the function f(x) = 1963?",
        "answers": ["0", "1963", "-infinity", "None of the above"],
        "correctAns": "0"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the integral of 1 with respect to x?",
        "answers": ["0.5x", "x+c", "1.25x", "2x"],
        "correctAns": "x+c"
    },

    {
        "question": "Who is the man credited with the discovery of calculus?",
        "answers": ["Edison", "Gottfried Wilhelm Leibniz", "Thomas Edison", "Georg Cantor"],
        "correctAns": "Gottfried Wilhelm Leibniz"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the derivative of f(x) = 3x² + 4x - 1 with respect to x?",
        "answers": ["6x + 4", "3x^2 + 4x", "6x + 4x -1", "6x - 4"],
        "correctAns": "6x + 4"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the limit of 1/(x - 1) as x approaches infinity?",
        "answers": ["infinity", "0", "-1", "-infinity"],
        "correctAns": "0"
    }, 

    {
        "question": "What is the derivative of x³ with respect to x? ",
        "answers": ["3x^2", "2x^3", "3x^2 + 1", "x^2"],
        "correctAns": "3x^2"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the integral of 2x with respect to x?",
        "answers": ["x² + c", "x²", "2x +c", "2x^2 + c"],
        "correctAns": "x² + c"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the second derivative of 4x⁴ + 3x² with respect to x?",
        "answers": ["12x³ + 6x", "12x³ + 6x + 3", "16x³ + 6x", "12x³ + 3x"],
        "correctAns": "12x³ + 6x"
    }, 

    {
        "question": "What is the limit of sin(x)/x as x approaches 0?",
        "answers": ["0", "1", "undefined", "-infinity"],
        "correctAns": "1"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the derivative of cos(x) with respect to x?",
        "answers": ["-sin(x)", "sin(x)", "cos(x)", "-cos(x)"],
        "correctAns": "-sin(x)"
    }

]